Barbara how wonderful thank you totally
wonderful what what a complete delight
and let's dive in and maybe have some if
you guys are up for some super sex are
you for uh sex alright so just want to
start with this this idea of the
evolutionary family the three of us have
talked about because it's such an
important idea and like many things
you've got glimmers of it in the great
traditions but it wasn't yet ready to
come into being because evolution hadn't
provided the conditions for it to emerge
so for example in Lauria in the 16th
century he talks about having a soul
root family people who are related to
your soul root that you recognize right
and in that recognition you come
together and you actually have deep
commitment and loyal to each other yes
and that emergence beyond biology which
is really where we're going you know
racism is kind of what the last vestiges
of being rooted in biology this movement
beyond biology and we get to kind of
choose our families and I think what you
said that you said so many things that
were so important but one of them was
that we have to be committed to them
yeah it's it's not just oh you're my
family often my family loved you it's
actually you're my family if you need
10,000 bucks I have it for you yes right
because what we do is we kind of pretend
to be evolutionary families but then
actually our real commitment right is to
biology and of course we want to
transcend and include we're totally
committed to the families were born with
because we've got something to work out
with them yes and that's destiny and
birth is destiny and we really choose
our families and we're really committed
to them yes and perhaps we even have you
know kinds of ceremonies right in which
people marry brothers can marry there's
West African tribes that have a male
marriage ceremony when brothers marry
when they choose each other or the
family chooses each other we actually
create rituals right to actually bring
this evolutionary family to existence I
do I do actually have a group of people
we haven't formalized it but these are
people that just they're my people and
they're available and there's I mean
there's a group of people that I'm in
touch with every day yes that are my
evolutionary family and and you know
it's really an emergent thing yes and
that's something that's beautiful I
think when I had my relationship with
Sydney I didn't do it because I had a
partner right and I used that partner
was my family right but so now I have to
create the family right by consciously
choosing and you have to be in touch
with people you can't you can't read you
can't write well let's do it right here
okay you guys up for it Emily for your
family yeah this is a good start this is
a toilet good start
I'm an this is an evolutionary family it
actually is always been like an
evolutionary son already yeah and you
yes yeah new evolutionary brother amen d
so committed great yeah here we are yes
you know baby the people watching this
future human becoming a future human
will want to choose their evolution yeah
at least two and you can do it right now
yeah who were those people they're
actually already there right there
artists have to name it and claim it
right gonna name a negative out it's
already been presented by reality and
you know you might say there are certain
things that you do you stay in touch
with each other number right which I'm
not good at you said you like you write
love letters outrageous love letters do
that we're gonna do that yes you're
going to do that with me so that that's
we do that as an evolutionary family
totally right outrageous love letters
outrageous love letters right - Daniel -
absolutely absolutely so a family act
one of the key ones is really seeing
each other right and the exercise you
kind of foreshadowed of with the power
vested in me I see you and go forth I I
just have to start by seeing something
in you that's so palpable is and this is
totally a unique self of Barbra and a
super sex comment it has when you're
talking
it is so intensely attractive and I
think everybody probably experiences
that I certainly do since the first time
we met and it's because there's a
there's a gestalt in your way of being
at kind of transmission of all of the
content you're saying or the way that
your being is completely a demonstration
incongruent with the content you're
saying yeah because you're teaching and
you're doing are an unavoidable
expression if we actually are and
there's really no difference between
them
and whenever someone's has awoken to
their unique self enough that they're
doing is the inescapable expression of
that and they're fused yeah then you see
someone's passion and identity in that
kind of fusion I think that's the most
attractive thing about humans it's when
the impulse of creation comes out as a
unique self and unique stuff it's also
in the voice remember I was talking
about bringing them so there's a
resonant tone and I can tell the
difference whether I'm really coming
from the unique self that the the voice
itself resonates with it the voice
absolutely distinguishes absolutely
distinguishes I mean really what you're
saying Daniel which is just so wildly
just good you feel the goodness of it
but not just the truth of it and the
beauty of it but the goodness of it is
that love and this is key to our
evolutionary emergence as a family and
as a species we said that you know and
week two that our love lists are too
short and and never marry for love
meaning great to love the one you marry
but if you look to marry for love and
then to get all of your love a need out
of that one relationship it's gonna
collapse because no one relationship can
provide it we've kind of exiled love
right into kind of a narrow frame of
romantic marriage then we've exiled it
further into heterosexual married and
then be exiled it further to the first
year I've had a reason right so what not
even right right if that's a love that
loves gotten very very small but love it
its core I think Daniel that's what you
were saying is love is a unique self
perception right to love a person is to
see them with God's eyes yes all right
it's to shift perspectives and to say
when you're living your unique self
right I'm alert to you and I'm attracted
to you because the the strange attractor
of unique self right brings me towards
you and when you shift love from an
emotion right at its core to a
perception at its core
for the first time you can train the
perception you can cleanse the doors of
perception the emotion comes hits you
today it's gone tomorrow that hit the
secretary up there that's somebody else
yeah but after you've had it's courts of
perception and out of the perception the
emotion emerges all of the sudden are
loveless skin very long and I think one
of the differences between what you call
normal human love and why it's been
relegated today infatuation place and
outrageous love is the difference of is
it really perceiving who they are as a
projecting fantasy absolutely a fantasy
and you're not really seeing them and
then it dies when interact with reality
absolutely and so to go a little bit
deeper with that one of the things that
I notice I'm really attracted to in
wanting to join evolutionary family with
people is the consistency of being that
who they are
when they're doing their teaching their
Dharma is always who they are right
right and that's kind of the cleanup
part of having owned the shadow of it
and some of the grown-up parts and so
you know in all the years Barbara I've
known you for those of you who are
watching the way that she is on tape is
the way that she always is first thing
in the morning right before bed and we
were joking behind the scenes the other
day that she's frothing with becoming as
a way of being but her being is just
doing that all the time because it's who
she is and in the same and that's why
I'm not just appreciating what your
teaching is but really respect the being
right and the same thing with Mark you
know his his comment about that love
expresses itself with commitment that
that $10,000 it was actually like one of
our first conversations when there's a
recognition of him offering in a real
way family ship and so I think that's
really important yeah and I think when
you take sex to Supra sex and you make
supra sex the impulse of creation within
you or the unique self and then I
believe that the native desire to join
to co-create is the most powerful
impulse we have it's more powerful than
to join to procreate right to join to
co-create because when you get near it
it's joyful and it turns on and it
creates the world that we want
see it creates the most beautiful world
we want to see it's co-creation yeah and
we have to talk about and we'll talk
about in the next session the
relationship between eros super sex and
sexuality like how do those actually
play with each other but just for now
right the phallus of super sex and the
receiving if you will kind of feminine
receiving vehicle right is the unique
self yeah the unique self both loves the
moment open yes alright a it kind of
more dramatically right the unique self
fuck's the moment open yes right right
and every moment actually you open
or loves you oh but that's that's
co-creation that's that right and the
super sex actually happens in and
literally every moment of reality yeah
and every moment is actually pregnant
with something that can be born in it
and every moments either open or closed
it's very very true and that I forgot to
mention in my talk to beware of super
sexual promiscuity right because if you
when I first got turned on to all of
this I would go to a party and I was
agreeing to write a book for somebody to
make a movie with someone else and to
you know do a talk with someone else and
that came back with all these cards and
I couldn't remember their names right so
I was the next morning after there
saying yes to too many projects right
because it's very attractive right so
one of the things of maturing in super
sexual co-creation
it's like if we said yes to do this
future human we agreed to do it and
we're doing it right and there were lots
of ins and outs and ups and downs but it
was an agreement and it then the
follow-on to this so this is something
that is very important to learn when you
are doing super sex because it's so much
fun is it's a commitment in a way the
project becomes your offspring right and
that and that no Daniel pick up on them
hearing you about say something go part
of the super sex teaching that I think
is so critical is Marc was talking about
great questions and as we're moving from
procreation to more co-creation there's
this question for all of us for the
feminine for new relationships to ask
what am I committed to create in the
world that
as significant as creating human life is
it engages as much of my capacity it
isn't just creating a human life but
what am i committing to show up what is
this partnership you know - yeah - yeah
to create that's that significant and
it's that rewarding that's that neural
chemically altering that's that you know
it right evolutionary that's a huge
question right and if we don't ask that
question then there's a purpose that
comes from procreation that isn't met
and we default to it right and our
population can't let us keep doing that
and when we speak about needing to get
to a steady-state population in the
challenge of it this actually answers
something so clear which is as you
talked about and it ties the conscious
evolution and super sex together which
is as evolution is moving from
unconscious to conscious that includes
regulation moving from unconscious to
conscious processes and getting the
aliveness that comes from procreation
engaged otherwise is a huge key of
making right and I want to say something
here that it is really a challenge for
many of us it's a discovering vocation
because vocation isn't just a
superficial purpose it's a calling that
comes from your your solo career choice
and a lot of people that I know and when
I teaching quite often is people say I'm
longing to find my vocation and I think
one of the things we need to cultivate
with future humans is becoming a future
human means you're finding that impulse
and it isn't just a job or a project
it's a calling of your soul and that is
needs to be nurtured it's not nurtured
usually in any schools yeah I mean it
took totally and maybe just to to wrap
this in three things one is commitment
that you're talking about Daniel
commitment and the ability to lighten
each other right you know you know as
you delighted in Barbara right you know
just kind of like and then and it this
is really important and I get to delight
in this moment in Daniel delighting in
Barbara right right you know and the
contraction of ego is why is he talking
about her why he's not talking about me
right but that's the ego does all the
time yeah exact thing you let he's like
he's delighting in her and then I
delight in him delighting in hers right
but but the commitment things really big
right because if we don't have
commitment it's not gonna work right and
commitment comes from the realization
that as unique cells we can actually
replace the old models so you talked
about in your third section you talked
about the emergence of the co-creative
masc yeah and what we need to do is is
as you kind of alluded and pointed
towards we need to replace the myth of
masculinity yes instead of having the
male as our friend Warren Farrell likes
to say being the disposable one yeah
right is the warrior who's the protector
who has 95% of the death jobs right the
mask on actually gets to be celebrated
for his unique self yes in which case
the feminine has to shift and actually
not only right admire the success object
right but actually admire the emergence
of the unique self just like the
masculine it has to adopt the feminine
and not only admire the sex object but
actually invite unique self so unique
self and and conscious evolution come
together to create a kind of structure
that allows for the economic shifts and
the familial shifts because as we
actually come together as a as a
co-creative evolutionary family and we
commit to each other were erotically
filled right we're alive
well that's a good place for the word
tell erotic tell iraqis bring up this
time but t loss meaning higher purpose
and evolution always has this purpose
moral more conscious life and arrows and
I think in the co-creative human there's
a real powerful
teller otic impulse yeah juicy love for
higher purpose that includes co-creating
with others it's really a lot of love in
there and that that tell erotic movement
we're kind of sending over to you now as
part of our extended family and
sometimes you don't know all your
cousins here's the assignment identify
four people that are part of your
evolutionary family all them together
and have a family meeting we'll see you
next session thank you